<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://thfgroup.co.in/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thfgroup.co.in/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://thfgroup.co.in/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>THF Group - News</title>
  <updated>2023-12-12T15:34:12+05:30</updated>
  <author>
    <name>THF Group</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://thfgroup.co.in/blogs/news/launch-winter-sale</id>
    <published>2023-12-12T15:34:12+05:30</published>
    <updated>2023-12-12T15:41:04+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thfgroup.co.in/blogs/news/launch-winter-sale"/>
    <title>Launch Winter Sale</title>
    <author>
      <name>TRINABH FOODS</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p data-mce-fragment="1">Are you a tea lover? Do you enjoy sipping on a warm cup of tea to start your day or relax in the evening? If so, we have some exciting news for you! To celebrate the launch of our brand new online store, we are offering a special 20% discount on all tea products for a limited time. This is an opportunity you don't want to miss!</p>
<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">Why should you take advantage of this discount?</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Tea has been enjoyed for centuries and is known for its numerous health benefits. From boosting your immune system to aiding in digestion, tea is a versatile beverage that can be enjoyed in many different ways. By taking advantage of our 20% discount, you can stock up on your favorite teas and explore new flavors without breaking the bank.</p>
<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">What types of tea products are available?</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Our online store offers a wide range of tea products to suit every taste and preference. Whether you prefer black tea, green tea, flavored tea, or classic and strong tea, we have you covered. We also offer a variety of tea accessories such as teapots, infusers, and mugs to enhance your tea-drinking experience.</p>
<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">How can you redeem the discount?</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Redeeming the 20% discount is simple. Just visit our online store and browse through our selection of tea products. Add your desired items to your cart and proceed to checkout. All the products are available at 20% off. It's that easy!</p>
<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">When does the discount expire?</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">This special 20% discount is only available for a limited time. Make sure to take advantage of it before it expires. Don't miss out on the opportunity to stock up on your favorite teas or try something new at a discounted price.</p>
<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">Final thoughts</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">As tea enthusiasts ourselves, we are thrilled to launch our online store and share our passion for tea with you. We believe that everyone should have access to high-quality tea products at an affordable price. That's why we are offering this special 20% discount. So go ahead, explore our online store, and treat yourself to some delicious teas. Your taste buds and your wallet will thank you!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
